<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://zachkirsch.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://zachkirsch.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-06-02T03:40:07-04:00</updated><id>http://zachkirsch.com/</id><title type="html">Zach Kirsch</title><entry><title type="html">Ciao (the goodbye one) from Milano!</title><link href="http://zachkirsch.com/abroad%20update/2017/05/08/ciao-the-goodbye-one-from-milano.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ciao (the goodbye one) from Milano!" /><published>2017-05-08T07:46:25-04:00</published><updated>2017-05-08T07:46:25-04:00</updated><id>http://zachkirsch.com/abroad%20update/2017/05/08/ciao-the-goodbye-one-from-milano</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://zachkirsch.com/abroad%20update/2017/05/08/ciao-the-goodbye-one-from-milano.html">&lt;p&gt;Hello!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First off, sorry for the 10-week hiatus. I’m leaving Milan in a few days, so I
figure I should send one last update before I go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since my last update, I’ve done a lot of traveling: Athens, Vienna, Budapest,
Madrd, Norway (Oslo, Bergen, Tromsø), Paris, Venice, Rome, Florence, Cairo,
Marrakech, Lisbon, and the Amalfi Coast. To not bore you, I’ll focus on the
highlights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Budapest:&lt;/strong&gt; I went with Ron to Budapest, and it’s a beautiful city. We walked to
the top of the Citadella, which has a great view of Budapest. Also at the top,
there were some guys playing the shell game - that game where someone hides a
bead under one of three bottlecaps and moves them around, and then you have to
guess which cup has the bottlecaps. (See below picture of the guy as he is
saying “no pictures.”) They’re total scams since the guys usually cheat, it’s
borderline impossible to win. Only a fool would be so falsely confident to
gamble at that game, you’d might as well just burn your money. I don’t think I
have to tell the rest of this story, but it ends with me leaving the the
Citadella with my wallet considerably lighter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/blog/img/5 - Shell Game Scammers.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Shell Game Scammers&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Madrid:&lt;/strong&gt; Madrid was great because a lot of my friends were in Madrid that
weekend. Ron, Sophie and Melissa study there, Dani came up from Grenada, and a
bunch of kids from Tufts came for their spring break. We spent a day in Retiro
Park, ate some churros, and like a true Madridian, didn’t get to bed until
seven in the morning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norway:&lt;/strong&gt; I spent a week, traveling solo, in Norway for my spring break. It was
weird being by myself for so long, but I enjoyed the short break from the fast
pace of study abroad. I started in Oslo - on my first night, I went to the
Operahuset (opera house) and ended up sneaking in during intermission to see
the second half of the opera Carmen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I took an overnight train to Bergen (do not recommend), where I was able to see
Norway’s famous fjords. They’re basically small rivers with steep cliffs on the
sides, formed slowly by glacial erosion. Fun fact, because of all the fjord
inlets in Norway, its coastline is longer than the US’s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Bergen, I went to Tromsø, which is still in Norway but over a thousand
miles north of Oslo. That far north, the major attraction is seeing the
Northern Lights (see below). They spectacularly light up the sky, and they seem
so choreographed it’s weird to think it’s just random collisions of gas
molecules that produce them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/blog/img/6 - Northern Lights.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Northern Lights&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Venice: Venice is another beautiful city, and I especially enjoyed it because I
was with my mom and sisters. A little after Venice, we met up in Milan, where
we got a fantastic dinner that was more like eating in an Italian grandma’s
kitchen than at a restaurant (Hostaria della Lanterna, if you find yourself in
the neighborhood).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/blog/img/7 - Venice with Girls.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Venice with Girls&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cairo:&lt;/strong&gt; I went with (brother) Noah to Cairo on Easter weekend. There was a
little bit of nervousness surrounding the safety of the trip, but we were
careful and everything was okay. We used a lot of Marriott points and lived
like kings (pharaohs?) for a few days. And, of course, we saw as much of
Ancient Egypt as we could. There wasn’t as many other tourists as I expected,
and Noah and I got to be in the Great Pyramid of Giza by ourselves. We were
warned many times not to lie in the tomb, and as tempting as it was, we
resisted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/blog/img/8 - Pyramids with Noah.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Pyramids with Noah&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Marrakech &amp;amp; Lisbon:&lt;/strong&gt; I met with with Noah and my dad in Morocco, where we spent
a few days touring around, going to souks, and spent a whole day visiting the
Atlas Mountains near Marrakech. It was an awesome trip, and different than any
of the other trips I’ve taken. After Morocco, we went to Lisbon. I was only
there for a day, so we walked around a lot and of course, got some very fresh
fish and seafood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/blog/img/9 - Lisbon with Dad and Noah.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lisbon with Dad and Noah&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amalfi Coast:&lt;/strong&gt; The last trip of abroad was down on the southern Coast of Italy.
I went with the guys that I live with and a bunch of other kids that are on my
program. We stayed in Cetara, where Andrea has a house that we stayed at. (To
jog your memory, Andrea is the awesome Italian guy that we live with here in
Milan.) We went to a bunch of neighboring towns, pretty much switching off
between bus and boat as our mode of transportation. It was one of the most
beautiful places I’ve ever been - I constantly felt that I could be stuck in a
post card. And it was also really great to spend my last trip just hanging out
with all the friends I’ve made here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/blog/img/10 - Amalfi.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Amalfi&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that my time here is ending, I’m definitely sad to leave since it’s been
such a great experience for me. But I’m also excited to get back home to the
States, see all my family and friends, go to restaurants I’ve been craving for
months, and even to start work (if I can remember what it’s like to have real
responsibilities after this four month vacation). I’ll be in Cleveland next
week, then in Boston the week after, then in New Jersey after that, and then in
San Francisco 6/4-6/10, so if you’re in those any of those cities during those
times, let me know!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Arrivederci!
Zach&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Hello!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Adventures and Misadventures</title><link href="http://zachkirsch.com/abroad%20update/2017/02/24/adventures-and-misadventures.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Adventures and Misadventures" /><published>2017-02-24T18:36:29-05:00</published><updated>2017-02-24T18:36:29-05:00</updated><id>http://zachkirsch.com/abroad%20update/2017/02/24/adventures-and-misadventures</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://zachkirsch.com/abroad%20update/2017/02/24/adventures-and-misadventures.html">&lt;p&gt;Hello!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s been almost 7 weeks since I’ve arrived in Milan, so I think it’s about
time I give you another update.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To sum up my abroad experience so far in one word: new. I am learning a new
language, meeting new people, trying new foods, visiting new places, and doing
my best to say yes when there’s an opportunity for a new kind of experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In being in a new environment, it’s impossible not to encounter some cultural
differences. I’ve run into a few that, though quite subtle, are actually pretty
important.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One difference is that while there is very little violent crime here in Milan,
there is a lot of petty crime (think pickpocketing, theft, home invasion). As a
result of this, people are very serious about locking their doors. If someone
is running into their apartment to grab an jacket, they will first close and
lock the door, get the jacket, and then come back. A second result of this is
that people are very serious about their keys. The front door of my apartment
building has a lock, and all the tenants (a few hundred) have identical keys
that open that lock. If a tenant loses their key, there is a risk that someone
will find the key, track down the apartment building it belongs to, and use the
key to gain access. (Crazy, I know). Therefore, if a tenant loses their key, he
or she must replace the lock, and replace the keys of every tenant in the
building. The total cost of this is about $3000. Long story short: it’s very
important to not lose your keys. Almost needless to say at this point, about
three weeks after I moved in, I lost my keys. (See below picture of me
stranded outside my apartment door with no means of getting in). To this day, I
have no idea where the keys are; I might have left them in a taxi, but I was
able to track down the taxi driver and he told me that he had no idea who I was
and that he didn’t have any keys. After about a week of high stress, I fessed
up. Fortunately, I was able to persuade the housing manager that since I lost
the keys very far away from the apartment, it is very unlikely that someone
could figure out where the keys belonged, so the whole lock and keys
replacement was unnecessary. I left out the fact that I didn’t know where I
lost the keys, so let’s keep that between us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/blog/img/1 - Keyless in Milan.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Keyless in Milan&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another subtle difference here that I bet you’ve never heard is that the weight
capacities listed in elevators are actually quite accurate. I’m guessing that
in the States, when you enter an elevator, you don’t check the listed weight
maximum and then proceed to ask every occupant their weight to calculate if you
should get on. Back home, I’ve always used the strategy “if I can fit, then I’m
sure the elevator can support me”, and it’s never failed. Unfortunately, that
strategy has not been as successful here. A few weeks ago, I was walking into a
building with some friends. Three of them walked into the elevator, and I
stepped in to be the fourth. One of the guys shook his head and pointed at the
capacity sign, which said the limit of the elevator was 300 kilograms (about
650 pounds). (We later calculated that our combined weight was 660 pounds). I
smiled and, knowing how successful my elevator-riding strategy had been, walked
in anyway without a worry. Somewhere between the first and second floors, the
elevator lurched and completely stopped. None of the buttons were working. We
waited a few minutes, designated a pee corner, tried to force the doors open -
you know, all the usual things when you get stuck in an elevator. Of course, I
felt terrible, since this could not be more obviously my fault. We ended up
using the alarm to call for help, and about an hour later, a repairman showed
up who was able to rescue us. It was definitely a memorable experience, but not
one I’m dying to repeat. Please see the below selfie to get a feel for the
environment of that elevator.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/blog/img/2 - A happy group in the elevator.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;A happy group in the elevator&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m happy to say that the positive experiences I’ve had so far have vastly
outweighed these not-so-positive ones. The highlight for me has been traveling.
My second week here I went to Bergamo, which is a small but beautiful city
about an hour from Milan. We saw some magnificent churches and some stellar
views of the city and the surrounding hills. A week after that I went to La
Thuile, which is a ski town in Italy right on the French border. It was unlike
any skiing I’ve done before. The mountains were enormous - it would take us
about 30 minutes to get to the top of the mountain via ski lift, and upwards of
an hour to ski all the way down. One day I skied into La Rosière, a ski town in
France on the other side of the range, and got some crepes. Overall, it was a
unbelievable experience that I hope I’ll get the chance to do again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/blog/img/3 - That's me in the picture I swear.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;That's me in the picture I swear&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next week I went to Dublin with Sophie and Melissa, two of my friends from
Tufts. We went to the Guinness Factory, and were showed how to pour “the
perfect pint of Guinness”. Guinness is interesting in that its taste is highly
dependent on how you pour it. There’s a very methodical process where you pour
at a specific angle, stop prematurely, let it sit for a period of time, and
then finish it off. When it comes out out of the tap it’s a light brown, and a
few minutes later it’s pitch black. I haven’t quite mastered the technique, but
I did teach myself to enjoy the taste, so I’m calling that a win.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last weekend I went to Amsterdam, with my friends Ron and Nikki, and Nikki’s
friend Mary. (See below picture of Ron and I fixing our hair before we take
a picture). It’s an awesome city. We walked around a lot, went to the Van Gogh
museum and the Rijksmuseum (another art museum), and the Heineken factory. We
went to a Chainsmokers concert which was pretty crazy and super fun. We got a
feel for what the culture was like and all in all, had a great trip.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/blog/img/4 - Pre-shot hair check.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Pre-shot hair check&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This weekend I’m staying in Milan, and I’m happy to have a little break from
travel. This is actually my last weekend in Milan before finals period in May
(lots of travel ahead!) so I’m making sure to take advantage. I’m really glad
that I chose Milan - there are very few tourists compared to other cities in
Italy, so I really feel like I am getting to experience what life is like for
people that actually live here. I was warned a few times going in that people
here are not very friendly, and I have to disagree. Everyone I’ve met has been
welcoming and understanding that my Italian is, for lack of a better word,
awful. If you are planning a trip to Italy, I recommend you make a pit stop
here. And if you are planning a trip to Milan in the next two months, please
let me know!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorry this was so long, but I hope you feel informed about my time here so far.
Looking forward to next weekend (Athens) and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ciao!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Hello!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ciao from Milano!</title><link href="http://zachkirsch.com/abroad%20update/2017/01/15/ciao-from-milano.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ciao from Milano!" /><published>2017-01-15T20:35:41-05:00</published><updated>2017-01-15T20:35:41-05:00</updated><id>http://zachkirsch.com/abroad%20update/2017/01/15/ciao-from-milano</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://zachkirsch.com/abroad%20update/2017/01/15/ciao-from-milano.html">&lt;p&gt;Hello family and friends,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are reading this, then it means that I thought you would be at least
remotely interested in my study abroad adventures! I’ll be sending out updates
periodically with how my semester in Milan is going. If you’d like to be
removed from the list, just let me know, and I will try my best to not be
offended.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I arrived in Milan on Tuesday morning, so I’ve been here almost a week. My
first impression of the city was that it is surprising how similar many things
are to the US. I’ve never been to Europe, and everywhere I’ve traveled to
before has had a culture that I could immediately feel was very different.
There’s little bartering for prices here, people often use Uber to get around,
and I haven’t been unable to find any products that I’ve needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the first few days, I did notice some differences. A small but
entertaining one is that people are obsessed with change. You will get a glare
if you don’t have exact change, and if you don’t, the cashier calculates
exactly what you should pay to minimize the change you will get back. I
usually just display all the coins that I have and let the cashier pick the
ones out of my palm. It’s kind of a trust exercise since I’m still mastering
the values of the different coins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an effort to experience the culture of Milan, I went to see a professional
soccer game on Thursday (AC Milan vs. Terino). The tickets were ten bucks, and
the game was really entertaining. We were up 1-0 the entire first half. Well,
I thought we were up 1-0. I found out at the start of the second half that I
had mixed up the teams and had been rooting for the away team for 45 minutes.
Fortunately, we came back and ended up winning 2-1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m living in an apartment that’s right in the heart of Milan. I’m living with
five other students that are studying here too, and one “community
assistant” (CA) who helps acclimate us to the city and hangs out with us. We
really lucked out with our apartment - it’s very nice and is in a great
location. Because we have a lot of space, we hosted a couple dinner parties
with other students on the program. We made a pumpkin risotto for the first
one, and linguini with octopus last night for our second one. I’m learning a
bit about cooking from our CA which has been cool, and maybe I’ll be able to
teach him some of my skills, like how to masterfully cook a cup of instant
Ramen noodles (the trick is to not add too much salt).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow I’m starting my classes. For the first three weeks, we are just
learning Italian (3 hours a day), which is much needed because I completely
helpless when it comes to conversing in Italian. Since I’ve come, I tripled my
Italian vocabulary: now, instead of just “ciao”, I know “scusami” and “buona
notte”. We haven’t registered for most of our other classes yet, but I did
sign up for one- it’s a service learning seminar and I’ll be spending 5 hours
a week at a nearby center to work with migrants who have recently come to
Italy. Like much of Europe, Italy has seen a large influx of immigration, and
is in need of people to help ease their transition. In some cases, they don’t
speak Italian well or at all, so as an English speaker I may be helpful for
communicating. I’m very excited to start the program and I hope that I’ll be
able to make a difference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that I’m mostly settled in, I’m starting to think about traveling in
Europe. I signed up for a skiing trip in the Italian Alps in a few weeks. It’s
been a while since I’ve skied, so I’m glad I have extensive training to fall
back on (“french fries to go, pizza to stop”). We are also planning a trip as
an apartment, but we haven’t decided on a city yet. I’m hoping to visit a lot
of different places over the next few months, and if you have any suggestions,
feel free to throw them my way. And if you find yourself in the Milan area,
let me know!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading this essay. Ciao!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Hello family and friends,</summary></entry></feed>